clearlogin.com 2018-05-03

# Privacy Policy | Clearlogin

This Statement of Privacy applies to the clearlogin.com and Clearlogin, Inc. and governs data collection and usage. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, unless otherwise noted, all references to Clearlogin, Inc. include clearlogin.com. The Clearlogin website is a software as a service site. By using the Clearlogin website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.

### Collection of your Personal Information

Clearlogin may collect personally identifiable information, such as your name. If you purchase Clearlogin’s products and services, we collect billing and credit card information. This information is used to complete the purchase transaction. We may gather additional personal or non-personal information in the future.

Information about your computer hardware and software may be automatically collected by Clearlogin. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the Clearlogin website.

Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through Clearlogin’s public message boards, this information may be collected and used by others.

Clearlogin encourages you to review the privacy statements of websites you choose to link to from Clearlogin so that you can understand how those websites collect, use and share your information. Clearlogin is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on websites outside of the Clearlogin website.

Clearlogin will never store identity provider credentials.  This includes, but is not limited to Active Directory, Amazon Web Services, Google Suite, and any other LDAP-based identity provider.  The only exception to this is Clearlogin Directory, since Clearlogin Inc. hosts this feature.

### Use of your Personal Information

Clearlogin collects and uses your personal information to operate its website(s) and deliver the services you have requested.

Clearlogin may also use your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from Clearlogin and its affiliates. Clearlogin may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.

Clearlogin does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties.

Clearlogin may share data with trusted partners to help perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to Clearlogin, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.

Clearlogin may keep track of the websites and pages our users visit within Clearlogin, in order to determine what Clearlogin services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within Clearlogin to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.

Clearlogin will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Clearlogin or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Clearlogin; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Clearlogin, or the public.

### Use of Cookies

The Clearlogin website may use “cookies” to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize Clearlogin pages, or register with Clearlogin site or services, a cookie helps Clearlogin to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same Clearlogin website, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the Clearlogin features that you customized.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Clearlogin services or websites you visit.

### Security of your Personal Information

Clearlogin secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other websites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) protocol.

### Children Under Thirteen

Clearlogin does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen. If you are under the age of thirteen, you must ask your parent or guardian for permission to use this website.

### Disconnecting your Clearlogin Account from Third Party Websites

You will be able to connect your Clearlogin account to third party accounts. BY CONNECTING YOUR CLEARLOGIN ACCOUNT TO YOUR THIRD PARTY ACCOUNT, YOU ACKNOWLEDGE AND AGREE THAT YOU ARE CONSENTING TO THE CONTINUOUS RELEASE OF INFORMATION ABOUT YOU TO OTHERS (IN ACCORDANCE WITH YOUR PRIVACY SETTINGS ON THOSE THIRD PARTY SITES). IF YOU DO NOT WANT INFORMATION ABOUT YOU, INCLUDING PERSONALLY IDENTIFYING INFORMATION, TO BE SHARED INTHIS MANNER, DO NOT USE THIS FEATURE. You may disconnect your account from a third party account at any time. Users may disconnect their accounts from third-party websites by using the customer administration tools supplied with the product.

### Google OAuth Scopes

Certain actions on Clearlogin will require authorization from Google to complete. To login to the Admin or User site with your Google account, we will request access to your email and profile to either identify your user in our system or create a new one. When you grant us admin access on the G Suite Sync Settings page we will request access to your G Suite User Directory for the purpose of Password Sync’ing from Clearlogin to G Suite, as well as for Directory Sync’ing from Google to Clearlogin Directory. When you grant us admin access on a G Suite Identity Source we will request access to your G Suite User Directory for the purpose of authenticating users into your Clearlogin User Dashboard and to update passwords within G Suite when a user performs a password reset. We will also request access to your Group Directory for use with G Suite Filters in Access Rules.

### Opt-Out & Unsubscribe

We respect your privacy and give you an opportunity to opt-out of receiving announcements of certain information. Users may opt-out of receiving any or all communications from Clearlogin by contacting us here:

  * Email: [feedback@clearlogin.com](mailto:feedback@clearlogin.com)
  * Phone: [844-253-2710](tel:844-253-2710)

### Changes to this Statement

Clearlogin will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. Clearlogin encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how Clearlogin is protecting your information.
